{
	"puzzleEnvironment": {
		"puzzleGame": {
			"puzzleObject": {
				"controls": {
					"returnToDrawer": "true",
					"showPositionOnBoard": "true",
					"rotate": "true",
					"bringToFront": "true",
		  			"bringToBack": "true"
				},
				"moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true",
				"multiplePuzzleSelect": "true"
			},
			"puzzleBoard": {
				"zooming": {
					"zoomMenu": {
						"chooseZoomPoint": "true",
						"chooseZoomValue": "true",
						"reset": "true"
					},
					"boarderPicture": "true"
				}
			},
			"puzzleShuffling": {
				"randomAngleRotation": "true",
				"changePuzzleOrdering": "true"
			},
			"puzzleDrawer": "true",
			"preview": "true"
		},
		"puzzleGenerator": ["JigsawPuzzle", "Jigsaw2Puzzle", "OtherPuzzle"],
		"imageLoader": "false",
		"imageGallery": "false",
		"puzzleNavigation": "true"
	},
	"mainPage": "true",
	"mainNavigation": "true"
}

{
	"AND": {
		"mainPage": "true",
		"mainNavigation": "true",
		"AND": {
			"AND": {
				"AND": {
					"OR":  {
						"chooseZoomPoint": "true",
						"chooseZoomValue": "true",
						"reset": "true",
						"bringToFront": "true",
		  				"bringToBack": "true",
					},
					"boarderPicture": "true",
				},
				"OR": {
					"returnToDrawer": "true",
					"showPositionOnBoard": "true",
					"rotate": "true"
				},
				"moveableOnPuzzleBoard": "true",
				"multiplePuzzleSelect": "true",
				"randomAngleRotation": "true",
				"changePuzzleOrdering": "true",
				"puzzleDrawer": "true",
				"preview": "true",					
			},	
			"OR":{
				"imageLoader": "false",
				"imageGallery": "false",
				"puzzleNavigation": "true",
			},
			"puzzleNavigation": "true",
			"puzzleGenerator": "[\"JigsawPuzzle\", \"Jigsaw2Puzzle\", \"OtherPuzzle\"]",
		}
	}
}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "AND":{
               "OR":{
                  "chooseZoomPoint":"true",
                  "chooseZoomValue":"true",
                  "reset":"true",
		  "bringToFront": "true",
		  "bringToBack": "true",
		  "boarderPicture":"true"
               },
		"boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "OR":{
               "returnToDrawer":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleGenerator":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}


{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}


{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['ANTI-JIGSAW']"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['ANTI-JIGSAW']"}}}

{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW2']"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW2']"}}}

{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW']"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW']"}}}

{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{"imageGallery": "true"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "imageGallery":"true",
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}

{"imageGallery": "false"}
{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"imageGallery":"false","puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}



{"OR": { "zoomCoordinates": "true", "zoomValue": "true" }
{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                   },
		  "AND": {
			"OR":{
                           "reset":"true",
		           "toBack": "true",
		           "toFront": "true",
		           "boarderPicture":"true"
                        },
		  	"zoom":"true"
		  }	
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}
{ "AND":{ "mainPage":"true", "mainNavigation":"true", "AND":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "zoomCoordinates":"true", "zoomValue":"true", }, "AND": { "OR":{ "reset":"true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "zoom":"true" } }, "returnItem":"true", "showPositionOnBoard":"true", "rotate":"true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true", "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true", "randomAngleRotation":"true", "changePuzzleOrdering":"true", "puzzleDrawer":"true", "preview":"true" }, "OR":{ "imageLoader":"true", "imageGallery":"true", "puzzleNavigation":"true" }, "puzzleNavigation":"true", "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } } }


{"toOmitCompletely": "true"}
{ "AND":{ "toOmitCompletely": "true", "mainPage":"true", "mainNavigation":"true", "AND":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "zoomCoordinates":"true", "zoomValue":"true", }, "AND": { "OR":{ "reset":"true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "zoom":"true" } }, "returnItem":"true", "showPositionOnBoard":"true", "rotate":"true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true", "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true", "randomAngleRotation":"true", "changePuzzleOrdering":"true", "puzzleDrawer":"true", "preview":"true" }, "OR":{ "imageLoader":"true", "imageGallery":"true", "puzzleNavigation":"true" }, "puzzleNavigation":"true", "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } } }

{"toOmitCompletely": "false"}
{ "AND":{ "toOmitCompletely": "false", "mainPage":"true", "mainNavigation":"true", "AND":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "zoomCoordinates":"true", "zoomValue":"true", }, "AND": { "OR":{ "reset":"true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "zoom":"true" } }, "returnItem":"true", "showPositionOnBoard":"true", "rotate":"true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true", "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true", "randomAngleRotation":"true", "changePuzzleOrdering":"true", "puzzleDrawer":"true", "preview":"true" }, "OR":{ "imageLoader":"true", "imageGallery":"true", "puzzleNavigation":"true" }, "puzzleNavigation":"true", "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } } }


{"zoom": "true"}

{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"OR":{"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "AND":{
               "OR":{
                  "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                  "zoomValue":"true",
                  "reset":"true",
		  "toBack": "true",
		  "toFront": "true",
		  "boarderPicture":"true"
               },
		"zoom":"true"
            },
            "OR":{
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{"zoomCoordinates": "true"}

{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoomCoordinates":"true",
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{"zoomValue": "true"}

{ "AND":{ "mainPage":"true", "mainNavigation":"true", "AND":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "AND":{ "OR":{ "zoomCoordinates":"true", "reset":"true", "toBack": "true", "toFront": "true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "zoomValue": "true", "zoom":"true" }, "returnItem":"true", "showPositionOnBoard":"true", "rotate":"true", "boarderPicture":"true" }, "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true", "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true", "randomAngleRotation":"true", "changePuzzleOrdering":"true", "puzzleDrawer":"true", "preview":"true" }, "OR":{ "imageLoader":"true", "imageGallery":"true", "puzzleNavigation":"true" }, "puzzleNavigation":"true", "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" } } }

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
 		   "zoomValue": "true",
		   "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "NOT ['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']", "AND": { "puzzleAlgorithmType": "['ANTI-JIGSAW']" }}

{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"['ANTI-JIGSAW']","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"NOT ['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}
{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "puzzleAlgorithmType":"['ANTI-JIGSAW']",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"NOT ['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}


{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['ANTI-JIGSAW']", "AND": {"puzzleAlgorithmType": "['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']" }}

{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"ALL ['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"ALL ['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}



{"puzzleAlgorithmType": "NOT ['JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2', 'ANTI-JIGSAW']"}

{"AND":{"mainPage":"true","mainNavigation":"true","AND":{"AND":{"OR":{"AND":{"OR":{"zoomCoordinates":"true","zoomValue":"true","reset":"true","toBack":"true","toFront":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"zoom":"true"},"returnItem":"true","showPositionOnBoard":"true","rotate":"true","boarderPicture":"true"},"moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true","multiplePuzzleSelect":"true","randomAngleRotation":"true","changePuzzleOrdering":"true","puzzleDrawer":"true","preview":"true"},"OR":{"imageLoader":"true","imageGallery":"true","puzzleNavigation":"true"},"puzzleNavigation":"true","puzzleAlgorithmType":"NOT ['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"}}}

{
   "AND":{
      "mainPage":"true",
      "mainNavigation":"true",
      "AND":{
         "AND":{
            "OR":{
	       "AND":{
               	   "OR":{
                       "zoomCoordinates":"true",
                       "zoomValue":"true",
                       "reset":"true",
		       "toBack": "true",
		       "toFront": "true",
		       "boarderPicture":"true"
                   },
		  "zoom":"true"
               },
               "returnItem":"true",
               "showPositionOnBoard":"true",
               "rotate":"true",
	       "boarderPicture":"true"
            },
            "moveableOnPuzzleBoard":"true",
            "multiplePuzzleSelect":"true",
            "randomAngleRotation":"true",
            "changePuzzleOrdering":"true",
            "puzzleDrawer":"true",
            "preview":"true"
         },
         "OR":{
            "imageLoader":"true",
            "imageGallery":"true",
            "puzzleNavigation":"true"
         },
         "puzzleNavigation":"true",
         "puzzleAlgorithmType":"NOT ['JIGSAW', 'ANTI-JIGSAW', 'JIGSAW2']"
      }
   }
}



if ({"AND": { "feat1": "true", "feat2": "false", "OR": { 
                    "feat3": "true",  "OR": {
"feat4": "true", "feat5": "true"}}, 
                "AND": { "feat6": "true"}}}) { /* code */ }




Table 2. Native vs. entire JSON configuration expressions in program flow – more complex conditions from hierarchic relations
Name of compared metric	Corr.	W	p value	95% CI	Est.	p > 0.05
Cyclomatic Number	0.5035					F
CyclomaticDensity						F
Halstead’s Bugs						F
Halstead’s Difficulty						F
Halstead’s Effort				-		F
Halstead’s Length						F
Halstead’s Time						F
Halstead’s Vocabulary						F
Halstead’sVolume						F


•	RQ3: How incorporation of helper naming made as wrapping of hierarchic conditions affect code complexity metrics compared to native conditions and hierarchic conditional object? 

